Good evening, welcome to BBC London.
晚上好，欢迎收看BBC伦敦频道
There's concern around the future workload for GPs in London,
伦敦全科医生未来的工作负担令人堪忧
after a survey has indicated that a third of GPs
一项调查显示，有三分之一的全科医生
are planning to retire in the next three years.
计划在未来三年内退休
The survey by London-wide local medical committees
这项由伦敦全境地方医疗委员会开展的调查
Polled 150 practices across the capital
调查了首都150家医疗机构
Which look after up to 1.75 million patients.
这些机构服务着近175万病患
Helen Drew reports.
本台记者海伦·德鲁报道
Lisa Harrod-Rothwell has been a GP for nearly 20 years.
丽莎·哈罗德-罗斯韦尔担任全科医生已近20年
She takes time out of her packed day of appointments
她在排满预约的繁忙日程中抽空接受采访
At this GP practice in central London
在伦敦市中心的这家全科诊所里
To explain the daily pressures.
为了说明日常的工作压力
I hate saying to people, I'm sorry,
我真的很不愿意对患者说抱歉
You've now veered into a second problem, you need to rebook.
你现在又出现了新的问题，需要重新挂号
I hate that because, for me,
我对此感到很难受，因为在我看来
Just having the whole picture makes so much more sense.
看清全局后，一切都变得豁然开朗
And it's so much more effective to be able to do that.
这样做确实事半功倍
But we have to do that because if I try
但我们不得不这样做，因为如果我试图
and deal with more than one problem
同时处理多个问题
in the time that I've got, I will make mistakes.
在有限的时间内，我肯定会出错
The situation could be about to get worse
局势恐怕还要雪上加霜
as research from London-wide local medical committees
根据伦敦全境地方医疗委员会的调研
shows more GPs are going to be leaving the profession.
显示将有更多全科医生离职
They surveyed over 150 practices
他们对超过150家诊所进行了调查
covering 1.75 million patients in the capital.
涵盖了首都175万患者
And found a third of practices have GPs
调查发现，三分之一的诊所都有全科医生
planning to retire in the next three years.
打算在未来三年内退休
More than half of practices say
半数以上的诊所反映
that current work pressures are impacting
目前的工作压力正严重影响着
the health of their staff and 21% say
医护人员的健康状况，还有21%的诊所声称
They're pessimistic about their ability
他们对自己能否胜任感到信心不足
to safely meet patient need over the coming months.
在未来几个月安全满足患者需求
Since COVID, more GP appointments are carried out remotely,
新冠疫情后，更多的全科医生问诊转为远程进行
but research shows that most patients still prefer in-person appointments,
但研究表明，多数患者还是倾向于当面就诊
which we found on the street.
这是我们在街头采访了解到的
It's always nicer to actually speak
面对面跟真人聊天感觉总是更好
to a proper human being face-to-face
跟真人面对面交流
and look them in the eyes, I think.
还能看着对方的眼睛，我觉得这样更好
It has to be face-to-face.
必须得是面对面才行
How can they tell over the phone? They can't.
电话里怎么能看得出来？根本看不出来
I think definitely face-to-face.
我觉得肯定是当面沟通更好
Over the phone I've never tried,
电话沟通的方式我还没试过
but I can appreciate that under pressure
不过我也能理解，在压力之下
they need to do both.
他们需要双管齐下
Numbers of fully qualified GPs
完全合格的全科医生数量
Have started to increase in the last 12 months,
近一年来已开始有所增长
But there are still fewer GPs now
但如今全科医生的数量依然较少
Than there were 10 years ago,
相比十年前有所减少
And they're looking after more patients than ever as the population increases.
而且随着人口增长，他们需要诊治的患者数量达到了历史新高
Helen Drew, BBC London.
BBC伦敦记者海伦·德鲁报道
The Department of Health and Social Care said
卫生与社会保障部表示
in this government's first year,
在本届政府执政首年
it's recruited more than 2,500 GPs
已成功招募逾2500名全科医生
and invested an extra £1.1 billion into general practice.
并向全科诊疗服务额外投入11亿英镑资金
There's speculation the Chancellor could use this week's budget
外界猜测财政大臣或将在本周预算案中
To introduce a new tourist tax for London.
伦敦计划开征新的旅游税
The Mayor, Sadiq Khan, is a fan of the idea.
市长萨迪克·汗对此提议表示支持
He says it would boost our economy
他表示这将促进经济发展
and help strengthen London's reputation
并有助于提升伦敦的声誉
as a global tourism and business destination.
作为世界级的旅游和商业中心
But the hospitality industry is worried
不过酒店业忧心忡忡
It could put people off.
这可能会吓跑游客
Here's John Harvey.
请看约翰·哈维发回的报道
It's being called a tourist tax.
这就是所谓的旅游税
Otherwise known as an overnight visitor levy,
也就是过夜游客附加费
It would see an additional charge
这将会产生一笔额外收费
Being added to the price you'd normally pay
这笔费用会加在您通常支付的住宿价格之上
For a hotel or Airbnb-style accommodation.
适用于酒店或爱彼迎这类住宿
The money raised would be used to fund improvements to the local area.
这笔筹集的资金将用于改善当地社区环境
It's already common across the world.
这种做法在全球范围内已经相当普遍
Cities like New York, Paris and Barcelona all have very similar charges in place.
纽约、巴黎和巴塞罗那等城市都已实行类似的收费政策
An estimate suggests it could raise anywhere between £100 and £500 million a year in London.
据估算，这项政策每年可为伦敦带来1亿到5亿英镑的收入
A spokesperson for the Mayor said he won't comment on speculation,
市长发言人表示，不会对坊间传闻作出回应
but that he's been clear in the past that a modest tourist levy would be good for the city.
但此前他已明确表态，认为适度的旅游税对城市发展大有裨益
Local councils, particularly in central London where they say high visitor numbers place pressure on local services,
地方议会，尤其是在游客众多给公共服务带来巨大压力的伦敦市中心地区
Are also keen on the idea.
同样支持这个想法
Westminster spends around £115 million a year servicing the visitor and commuter economy.
威斯敏斯特区每年投入约1.15亿英镑来维持游客和通勤者相关的经济活动
And obviously we want to be able to ensure that that money can help secure those services.
显然，我们希望确保这笔资金能够切实保障相关服务的正常运转
That's ensuring our streets are kept clean, streets are kept safe
这包括确保街道整洁有序、治安环境良好
And making sure that we have a welcome environment for visitors to both Westminster and across London.
同时为来到威斯敏斯特乃至整个伦敦的游客营造宾至如归的环境
But the trade body representing UK hospitality businesses has called the proposal shocking.
然而，代表英国餐饮酒店业的行业协会直呼这项提案太离谱了
Overseas visitors are incredibly important to central London,
海外游客对伦敦市中心来说至关重要
but across London as a whole, it is builders who are coming to work,
但从整个伦敦来看，更多的是来打工的建筑工人
it is businesses coming to conferences, it's family coming for concerts and theatres
是来开会的商务人士，是来看演唱会、逛剧院的家人
and going to see family and friends.
还有来探亲访友的游客
This will have a really big impact on British consumers.
这对英国消费者来说影响可不小
It's attacks on hard-working British families having a short break in London
这简直是在针对那些在伦敦短暂度假的勤劳英国家庭
and it will deter visitors from coming in.
而且还会吓跑想来旅游的游客
The government told us that they are always open to hearing views from local leaders on issues like this,
政府表示，他们一向乐于听取地方领导对此类问题的看法
but won't comment on budget speculation.
但不愿对预算方面的猜测性言论置评
The question now is whether the Chancellor will sign off on the idea
眼下大家最关心的是，财政大臣会不会点头同意这个方案
and tourists will have to wait and see whether a trip to
游客们只能拭目以待，看看去
the capital will come with a little extra on the bill.
首都旅游会不会在账单上多出一笔额外开销
Jonny Harvey reporting.
乔尼·哈维为您报道
Now for your weather forecast with Alexis.
接下来由亚历克西斯为您播报天气预报
Good evening. Through the course of the overnight period, it will be dry at first,
晚上好。夜间开始时天气干燥
but we will see a few showers drifting in ahead of a band
但随后会有零星阵雨，接着是一片雨带到来
of rain which will arrive during the early hours of the morning
雨带将在清晨时分抵达
with increasing clouds and many places seeing that cloud and also the outbreaks of rain during the early hours.
云层逐渐增厚，清晨时分多地会出现阴云和降雨
Temperatures will drop away to around three to four Celsius, so it's a wet commute to work tomorrow.
气温将降至3到4摄氏度左右，明天上班路上会遇雨
There will be a good deal of rain first of all, followed by some dry and bright periods,
先是会有不少降雨，之后会迎来几段干燥晴朗的天气
also a few scattered showers or outbreaks of rain as we head through the course of the afternoon.
下午时段还会出现零星阵雨或降雨
The showers will be interspersed by areas of thicker cloud,
阵雨间会有较厚的云层
but also some brighter spells with highs of seven to eight degrees.
同时也会有阳光较好的时候，最高气温七到八度
Here's the outlook for the rest of the week, turning cooler tomorrow and more so into Tuesday.
接下来一周的天气展望：明天开始转凉，周二会更冷一些
We could see a widespread frost Tuesday night into Wednesday morning,
周二夜间至周三清晨，预计会出现大范围霜冻天气
But lots of sunshine is expected on Tuesday, highs of eight degrees.
不过周二阳光充足，最高气温将达到八度
Temperatures rise as we head through Thursday and Friday.
周四和周五气温将逐步回升
I'll be back with your late news just after half ten tonight.
今晚十点半之后，我将为您带来晚间新闻播报
Have a good evening. Goodbye.
祝您晚安，再见